in this video I'm going to explain to
you exactly how I made
$345,000 in one single trade so you guys
can see it right here this was on April
that I had my biggest trade ever and as
you guys can see there might be 1 2 3
four five six different positions and
you're probably asking yourself why is
there so many different positions why
don't you just take one big trade that's
simply because I cannot execute the big
of the lot size that I would want to in
one single position why because the
slippage would be ridiculous the market
simply does not have access to liquidate
that position within seconds as I
expected so what I place is a 90 lot
every single 5 six seconds so the market
has time to catch my trade and I don't
catch slippage and this is pretty much
why I have to divide the trade in six
different ways because what I'm risking
obviously I'm trading a really big
account is that's the proportion to you
know 2 3 4% of the account so to keep it
a very simple analogy it's like if you
were to want to travel to let's say
Mexico and when you travel to Mexico
you're going to be there for a month you
have to take a lot of your clothes well
you can't fit everything inside a one
luggage just simply doesn't happen it's
not going to work you have to take about
five six different carry-ons boook bags
whatever to make everything fit but it's
all going to the same destination which
is Mexico that you're going for the trip
in this case we were taking the same
exact trade we were selling GBP but we
were just entering the same exact
position just a bunch of different
little entries so if you were to go to
Mexico you're on the same plane on the
same route you're just having a bunch of
little carry-on bags versus literally
having to have a vehicle full of
clothing that realistically that can't
happen because it doesn't fit on the
plane it's just not going to happen well
same thing in the market I can't take
one big position because the Market's
not going to liquidate it it's not going
to execute and the slippage is going to
be ridiculous so now that you understand
that let me actually break down the
trade and exactly what I did in order to
make
$345,000 so let's begin all right so now
that we're here in the market this is
the actual trade that made me
$345,000 as you guys can see we are
currently on the daily time frame on GBP
Cad and this trade took about 1 two
three and a half days to play out so I
am more of a interday day trader SL
swing Trader but trades like this happen
all of the time in the market and I've
been honestly mastering these lately
where I pretty much only have to hold
for about 2 3 days and it gives me a
beautiful one to two risk to reward so
in this trade is where I had the biggest
trade setup that I have ever had but
it's a very textbook trade anybody could
have caught this and the way you simply
have your profits is deciding on what
you're going to risk so I'm going to
actually explain to you how I identified
this trade and how I capitalized off of
it so first things first before I enter
any single position I need to understand
the trend of the market what is the
market doing so in this example right
here the market was bullish the market
in this example right here it was
creating higher highs and higher lows
very simple very straightforward you
have a higher high higher low higher
high higher low higher high and then as
you can see right here the market
shifted bearish with this humongous
bearish candle now this market now went
from being bullish to now completely
shifting and now being bearish so if I
were to Simply get this line chart right
here that we literally just drew which
is the same exact Market structure but
just on the line chart or if we were to
actually just put the line chart you can
see obviously the same thing this just
looks a lot more clear you can see how
this Market created a head and shoulders
so head and shoulders are massive
reversal patterns and obviously the
higher the time frames that these happen
at the better so as you can see this
head and shoulders has happened at a
high of the market and has had a
humongous bearish engulfing Candlestick
breaking the neckline confirming it is a
head and shoulders so you only have a
valid Head and Shoulders once you have
broken the neckline and it's created but
now you can't enter a position on the
bottom of the move you have to wait for
the retracements of the neckline of The
Head and Shoulder shoulders to then
enter the trade this is where price is
going to retest the neckline and then
obviously the trade will then head to
the downside well that is exactly what
we did right here we waited for price to
come back and retest the neckline of The
Head and Shoulders along with an area of
interest but all of this was identified
by first things first this is Market
structure as soon as you understand
where the market structure is headed you
will understand where the rest of the
trade is going to be but without you
knowing where the market is headed you
simply do not know what you're going to
execute so not only did we have a daily
Head and Shoulders pattern if we were to
go down to the 4-Hour time frame you can
see how the 4-Hour time frame was in a
beautiful bullish Channel even though I
hate to use these things because they're
super subjective but you know just to
keep it to eye candy and very obvious
you can see how we're pretty much going
upwards we're in a beautiful bullish
Market trend
and as you can see we had a breakout of
that beautiful uptrend not that this
channel matters not that we use this
ever but it's just so you can visually
notice that this Market is bullish and
that this Market was heading to the
upside now what we are going to do if
the Market's heading to the upside we're
going to buy because that is what the
market structure is doing at that point
and we were actually entering buy
positions while this Market was going up
but this market then shifted which is at
this point right here here it's where it
had this humongous selloff and it's
pretty much the breakout of this channel
which is the breakout of the market
going up or going down and then as soon
as you have that breakout you can't
enter at the lower low of the breakout
pretty much the move is gone you have to
wait for price to have a retracement so
here's where I went down to the 4-Hour
time frame I identified my area of
interest and an area of interest is
identified by a zone that has three or
more touches an area interest is only
valid if you have three touches or more
now the touches have to be with the body
candlesticks you can have them with the
wick but you have to just simply ask
yourself would you rather enter a trade
that it has a rejection from a wick or
from a structure Point what do you think
is stronger obviously the structure
point the wick is pretty much like the
trail and the trail is not what you want
to base off your Market structure move
because if you notice this exact move
right here we can count this Wick right
here and when we were to go to the
market structure that simply doesn't
exist why because it's just a wick it's
a trail it's not real in a way it's just
you show it's just the market showing
you where it was in the past but it's
not where it actually closed in real
time the trail should never be used as a
point of an area of interest you only
want to use the market structure so now
that we identified this area of Interest
right here because we have this
structure point right here this is one
then we have this structure point which
is two and then we have this structure
point which is three now we have a valid
area of Interest so now we have the
daily time frame bearish 4H hour time
frame bearish and now we have a solid
area of Interest along with daily Head
and Shoulders notice how I have just
added four reasons on why we should
enter this trade to the downside versus
continue to buy to the upside because
again remember at the end of the day the
market is going to Simply go up or it's
going to go down it's going to do one or
the other if it ever does something you
let me know please cuz I have not seen
the market do that yet so when the
market is going to go up or down you
just simply find more reasons on why
it's going to go down rather than up
it's really that easy so based off of
what we have just identified it just
simply makes sense as of right now with
four different reasons why should
continue to go to the downside so once
prices had this pull back to the area of
Interest I go down to the 4-Hour time
frame and then I start pretty much
looking at what else can I add as a
reason in order to enter this trade now
obviously I have a whole entire
checklist with my strategy that I pretty
much check off every single time I'm
looking to enter a trade if certain
things don't check off I simply do not
take the trade so as you can see we also
have an added Confluence which is our
EMA is under the price price which is
good because the EMA is used as a
dynamic level of support and resistance
but it's an indicator so this indicator
if price is under it it's resistance it
should continue to sell if price is
above it it's used as support it should
continue to go up well not only did we
just shift out of the channel but now we
are under the EMA as well so it's an
added Confluence and now we are at five
reasons on why we should be entering
this trade to the downside and just to
show you a very simple example right
here when this Market was in this
bullish Channel at this point you guys
can see how the EMA was holding up price
while it was inside of this bullish
channel so the EMA works as an added
Confluence to be used as a dynamic level
of support and resistance it doesn't
always have to touch it perfectly it's
just to have your perspective and your
knowledge so you can notice hey we are
above it that's another reason why we
should enter the trade or avoid the
trade so after we identify that we have
price under the EMA I would want to come
into the live price of where price
actually is well once we are here at
this point this is where I was actively
looking at this trade I'm like well this
pattern looks familiar and if you've
seen the Candlestick bable or super
basic trading stuff you can tell that
this right here is a beautiful double
top formation now we have a double top
form
at a area of interest at the neckline of
The Head and Shoulders under the
EMA this is pretty much is telling us
it's going to go down like why would
this go up with all those reasons find
me a reason on why this should go up
versus down there's not that many or if
there is the ones to sell outweigh the
ones to go up and that's all you need in
order to have an edge in the market so
this is where I identified a beautiful
double top but obviously after this
humongous bearish candlestick I cannot
take the trade so this is where I waited
for price to have a pull back into this
neckline of the double top and at this
point right here is where I executed
this position so I executed this
position at this point right here where
we had created a little bearish
engulfing Candlestick which is by far my
favorite entry signal I will not take a
trade if I do not have a bullish or
bearish Eng golfing Candlestick and once
I saw this bearish engulfing Candlestick
pretty much executed the trade right
there at that spot so you guys can see
that we are having our stop loss above
the EMA and above other stuff so
literally it right now kind of annoying
this spread is so [__] crazy bro I
[__] hate it but it is what it is
it's part of the game because as you can
see price was creating higher highs and
higher lows but then we shifted the
structure pulled back to to retest the
structure retest the neckline of the
double top and then we had a bearish
engulfing and what else do we have here
we also have a rejection from under the
1H hour EMA so notice how many things I
am adding to this trade that is simply
just an accumulation of reasons on why
they should go to the downside so I
simply executed the trade at that point
where I had about 8 to n confluences all
overall in order to take this position
to the downside soon as I execute the
position well before I execute the
position I have to obviously set my
stop- loss and set my takeprofit because
I can do this whole entire analysis
pretty much dedicate a whole week
waiting for this to give me a nice setup
but if at the moment that I'm going to
execute the trade the risk to reward
does not make sense I do not take the
trade I can wait for a trade for six
months and when it comes to the point to
enter literally as soon as I'm about to
hit the enter point I'm like hold on is
the risk reward worth it yes or no and
in this case it was but there's many
times where I have had other positions
that the risk reward is not worth it and
I will not take the trade because that
is the edge in the market if you have a
positive risk to reward you will be
successful in trading if you do not have
a positive risk reward you will not be
successful in trading it is that simple
telling you right now that took me like
4 years to figure out fully but don't
let that go over your head so I always
play place my stop loss as soon as I'm
going to enter the position at the point
where I believe if the market hits that
point we are now going to be completely
wrong and it's going to go the complete
other way so I put my stop loss based
off of the 4our high point so this is
the point where I believe if the market
body closed Above This zone right here
Not only would we have closed above the
EMA but we would have closed above or
into the area of Interest where price
could have used this area as a support
point to then head to the upside so I
plac my stop loss strategically if I am
wrong on this position I was wrong as a
whole meaning the market Trend the
structure everything was just simply not
in my favor and the market is going to
have a complete reversal I don't want to
put my stop loss at a point where I can
potentially Get Wicked out and then the
market continue to go in my direction
cuz that it simply does not make sense
let's say if I were to put my stop loss
at a point like right here this if the
market were to hit that point the market
is still bearish it is still under the
EMA still under the structure point and
it's still under the area of Interest
Market can easily have a pull back into
this point and then head to the downside
without having the market completely
shift and my trade being wrong and
perfect example is exactly what happened
as soon as I entered the trade literally
I'm talking about about seconds I went
straight into drw down like immediately
into drw down on this position but I
strategically placed my stop- loss at a
point where if it would get hit I would
be completely wrong so I gave this a
plenty of space and it came into draw
down but what happened all of the
reasons on why I'm taking the trade
continue to help and push this trade to
the downside so we did have a little bit
of a push to the upside but the EMA the
area of Interest the market Trend the
neck lineer The Head and Shoulders the
structure everything was now in this
favor to continue pushing it to the
downside the market structure is going
to Simply follow the trend always so
this is where I placed my stop loss at a
point where it would be very difficult
for it to get hit and if it gets hit I
am completely wrong so then this is
where the market is at the stop loss but
stop- loss is just the first part of it
second part is your take profit where
are you going to get out because I can
have my stop loss good but if my stop
loss is too big and it simply doesn't
make sense for my takeprofit and I would
to have anything under a 1 to 2.5 I will
not execute this trade I do not execute
a trade unless I have a minimum of a 1
to 2.5 years to reward so I
strategically place my stop loss at this
structure point right here which I saw
as the next point where the market has
had very strong rejection in the past so
if we were to be looking at this market
like this which is exactly how I was
looking at it before entering the trade
I have to ask myself okay is the market
going to come into this point right here
which is this structure point and have a
rejection well we kind of only have one
structure point from here so the odds
are not really I feel like the market
can definitely break through this area
and continue to go so if the market were
to be able to break through this area
what would be the next area that it can
possibly reach where it can have a
reaction from and Market have a
rejection well I continue to drag this
down down down down and then I reach
this point right here and I notice when
I look to the left we have one structure
point two structure points three
structure points and if we keep looking
left we have four five so on and so
forth now this is a valid level of
support and resistance right because an
area of Interest needs to have more than
three touches two touches as resistance
two touches as support one resistance as
long as it has three structure points
and this area right here whenever we are
above we're heading up whenever we're
under we're heading down well if the
market is headed to that point that
means that we are going to be above that
zone so if we're going to be above it I
have to get out before it has a
rejection because we are above it and I
am in a sell position so I'm pretty much
selling into the lowest points of the
ground that I can get to I just have to
make sure I get out before we hit that
lowest point because that's where the
Market's going to have a reversal and
then go to the upside so this is where I
set my takeprofit because I saw it as
the next point where the market is going
to have a reaction from and when I
calculated my risk to reward as you can
see it was a 1 to
2.1 so my ideal risk reward is always a
a minimum of a 1 to
2.5 which realistically wasn't much else
when it comes to this trade but I
decided that I was very confident it and
I was extremely extremely uh invested
into it due to the fact that hundreds of
thousands of people saw me enter this
trade and all right you guys could have
literally not said that I did not show
you guys this literally to Perfection I
literally explained it to you guys
obviously and throughout the week I even
said one more trade I sent it inside the
free telegram I've been literally
sending it here it's literally all here
it's in the free telegram 100,000 100 4
142,000 holy [__] I said it right here
too at the beginning of the week my
mission is I just trade up on my
Instagram for literally a whole entire
week that I was already invested into
the position and there was absolutely
nothing wrong with it I didn't break one
single rule um and I accepted the risk
of taking a position with a 1 to 2.1
risk to reward that 0.4 not a big deal
as long as you have a minimum of a 1 to
2.5 for this trade specifically I
decided to take that risk but you know
luckily it played off and it played off
very well so this was at the point where
I had my takeprofit set so now that I
had my stop- loss and my takeprofit I
realized that okay now this trade makes
sense as soon as this trade makes sense
well now is when I'm going to actually
execute the position and this is exactly
where I executed the position right
there as soon as I executed the position
the position pretty much went straight
into drop down but I had absolutely no
emotion towards it because I know my
stop loss was at a point that it was
above the EMA and above the area of
interest and if it got hit I would be
completely wrong and then shortly after
that I can see the market creating
little head and shoulders right here
left head and a right shoulder and then
as soon as we broke through that
neckline it was pretty much green light
for me set and forget let the trade hit
your takeprofit but I the most
interesting part of this was that the
position was reaching Friday and as soon
as the position was reaching Friday
obviously the market closes but I wasn't
at my full takeprofit and I had a
decision to make I either closed at
where I was at at that point where I
believe I was at about 130 140,000 so I
held through the weekend we were up
about I saw a quarter I literally saw
250 up there uh for a second and I just
put my phone away cuz I just wanted to
focus on this right here I see so much
potential on this trade right here that
I just don't want to focus on the money
to focus on the trade so or do I stick
to my trading plan and do I hold
throughout the weekend now keep in mind
this is something that I have not done
in over eight months I have not held a
trade in a very long time simply because
I don't I don't I don't need to I
usually catch my trades throughout the
week and I get out and if for whatever
reason the trade does not reach my
takeprofit by the end of the week I just
literally close it out there the broker
fee are ridiculous holding throughout
the weekend and I just simply don't want
to pay them so I rather just get my
profits by the end of the week and if it
continued to go throughout the other
week so be it but for this position I
was so confident in the market structure
the trend the area of Interest The Head
and Shoulders pattern the shift of the
channel that it just simply made so much
sense to hold throughout the weekend
that's where I decided to pretty much
set and forget and as soon as the market
opened on the following week it went
immed mediately all the way to the next
take profit which was exactly where I
had anticipated this
trade video Yeah 100% all right so
basically these are all the sales that
we're tracking because you can see there
there's some they're not but you can see
how on the way to the takeprofit it was
creating little head and shoulders
pattern so this right here is a head and
shoulders pattern right here this one is
a head and shoulders on the 1 hour time
frame which it was are confirming to me
that this Market will continue to head
in that direction and this not only gave
me more confidence to continue to set
and forget but it it just confirmed the
market structure the trend that
everything I had uh previously analyze
is extremely valid so this right here is
where my takeprofit was hit and
obviously as soon as I close it I'm
seeing it continue to go to the downside
pretty much rethinking my whole life I'm
like wow I could have probably made half
a million on this but you know what did
not get greedy I simply realized that I
took the position that I should have
taken and my takeprofit got hit and that
is the trade and following my trading
plan exactly what I had explained I plac
my takeprofit at the perfect points that
if the market were to hit it it would
obviously have a push to the upside
because again whenever we are above this
area we're heading up whenever we're
under we're heading down so I got out of
the position before we got to that
points and had a reaction to the upside
So I placed my entry perfectly my stop
loss at a perfect point that if it were
to get hit I would be completely wrong
and I placed my takeprofit perfectly to
the last point that the market was going
to reach to before I had a push to the
upside and this trade right here what
you see is what I do literally every
single week with my students I literally
called this trade with my students on
Sunday swings because I got on a call
every single Sunday with my students
that I give them my top two and top
three pairs that I'm going to be trading
for the week myself and this is why
they're able to generate anywhere from a
th000 to
$1,500 a week as a beginner set and
forget Trader so if you don't know what
set and forget is and you want to know
more about it make sure you click the
link in the description below and you're
going to know exactly what set and
forget is and how it lets Traders make
anywhere from ,000 to
$11,500 a week as a beginner set and
forget Trader so if you guys want to see
more videos like this and you guys liked
it make sure to hit that like And
subscribe button because because big
trades like this is honestly becoming
The New Normal I had a
$162,000 trade about a month ago and
this about 2 weeks ago so I'm excited to
see what this year has to bring and what
new records I will be breaking so if you
guys want to make sure you tune in learn
and capitalize off of these
opportunities as well make sure you hit
that like And subscribe button and I'll
see you guys in the next One S and
forget